

#### **Emanuel Fernandes Azevedo**

Lugar do Boucelinho 4540-209 Burgo, Arouca

910028599

### **Profile**

Graduate in Technologies of Information at School of Technologies and Management of Águeda in 2018. At the moment studying Master's degree of Communication and Multimedia, in the area of Interative Multimedia at Aveiro University.

I have experience in backend and frontend, being more interested in the last one and in the use of technologies like *ReactJS*.

# **Professional Experience**

### Best Content Unipessoal, Lda. - Fullstack/Lead Developer

Nov 2019 - Nov 2020

Development of a web aplication for digital marketing planning and management

- Fullstack development and maintenance of a web aplication with *Vue* and *Laravel*
- Maintenance of a web aplication with Vue and Laravel
- Management of the application and websites servers

### Digitalmente Lda. - Fullstack Developer

Fev 2018 - Maio 2018

Development of a web aplication for managing portfolios and employees of an energy company – curricular internship

- Fullstack development of a web application with AngularJS and Symfony
- Development of automatic application tests with Katalon/Selenium and Java

### **Education**

**Master of Communication and Multimedia - Interactive** 

Set 2019 - Now

Multimedia

**Aveiro University** 

**Isolated Curricular Units** 

Set 2018 - Jul 2019

of Master of Communication and Multimedia

**Aveiro University** 

**Degree of Technologies of Information** 

Set 2015 - Jul 2018

School of Technologies and Management of Águeda

## **Formation**

**Wallstreet English Aveiro** 

Out 2018 - Out 2020

Level reached: C2

First Certificate in English: B2